{
    "questionlist": [{
            "cardfront": "健身房",
            "cardback": "GYM"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "菲律宾",
            "cardback": "Philippines"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "骑车",
            "cardback": "to cycle"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "晴天",
            "cardback": "sunny day"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "健康",
            "cardback": "health,healthy"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "锻炼",
            "cardback": "to work out"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "放",
            "cardback": "to put"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "影响",
            "cardback": "influence"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "口渴",
            "cardback": "thirsty"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "宾馆",
            "cardback": "guesthouse"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "旧",
            "cardback": "old/former"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "教室",
            "cardback": "classroom"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "丈夫",
            "cardback": "husband"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "校长",
            "cardback": "headmaster"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "多次",
            "cardback": "repeatedly"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "遇到",
            "cardback": "to run into"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "词语",
            "cardback": "a word"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "铅笔",
            "cardback": "a pencil"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "旁边",
            "cardback": "to the side"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "决定",
            "cardback": "to decide"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "阴",
            "cardback": "overcast"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "怕",
            "cardback": "to fear"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "字典",
            "cardback": "Chinese vocabulary"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "提高",
            "cardback": "to improve"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "洗碗",
            "cardback": "wash the dishes"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "清楚",
            "cardback": "clear"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "黑板",
            "cardback": "blackboard"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "结婚",
            "cardback": "to marry"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "努力",
            "cardback": "to try hard"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "练习",
            "cardback": "to practice"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "总是",
            "cardback": "always"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "满意",
            "cardback": "satisfied"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "其实",
            "cardback": "actually"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "主",
            "cardback": "host"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "介绍",
            "cardback": "to introduce"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "表演",
            "cardback": "a show"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "节目",
            "cardback": "program"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "刻",
            "cardback": "quarter(time)"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "裤子",
            "cardback": "trousers"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "放",
            "cardback": "10 cents"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "被",
            "cardback": "by (passive voice)"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "办法",
            "cardback": "method/way"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "解决",
            "cardback": "to solve"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "根据",
            "cardback": "according to"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "刮风",
            "cardback": "to be windy"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "愿意",
            "cardback": "to wish"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "附近",
            "cardback": "nearby"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "注意",
            "cardback": "to pay attention to"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "段",
            "cardback": "paragraph"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "表示",
            "cardback": "to express"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "理解",
            "cardback": "to find out"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "变化",
            "cardback": "to change"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "热情",
            "cardback": "passionate"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "行礼箱",
            "cardback": "suitcase"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "收入",
            "cardback": "income"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "麻烦",
            "cardback": "inconvenient"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "即使",
            "cardback": "even if"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "菠菜",
            "cardback": "spinach"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "莳萝",
            "cardback": "dill"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "躺",
            "cardback": "to lie down"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "全部",
            "cardback": "entire/whole"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "放假",
            "cardback": "to have a holiday"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "放学",
            "cardback": "to dismiss students"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "放学后",
            "cardback": "after school"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "放血",
            "cardback": "to let blood"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "放屁",
            "cardback": "to fart"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "填写",
            "cardback": "to fill in the form"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "时装模特",
            "cardback": "fashion model"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "羽绒服",
            "cardback": "down-filled garment"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "举行",
            "cardback": "to hold(a meeting)"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "敢",
            "cardback": "to dare"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "擦",
            "cardback": "to wipe"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "地板",
            "cardback": "floor"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "拔罐",
            "cardback": "cupping(ChM)"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "三文鱼",
            "cardback": "salmon"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "针灸",
            "cardback": "acupuncture"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "疗法",
            "cardback": "therapy"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "胃灼热",
            "cardback": "heartburn/pyrosis"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "估计",
            "cardback": "to estimate"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "刺激",
            "cardback": "to provoke"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "荞麦",
            "cardback": "buckwheat"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "厚",
            "cardback": "thick"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "睫毛",
            "cardback": "eyelashes"
        },
        {
            "cardfront": "化妆",
            "cardback": "to put on makeup"
        }


    ]
}